Ari, Lulu, Mei, Hime, Riai, Ichiko, Lisa, Kisaki, Sakura, and Akari.
I think we have prepared more than twice as much as we should have, so let's give it our all and have fun.
Let's not only give it our all, but also have fun and let the audience see what Juice- Juice is all about now.
Let's just have fun and let the audience see what Juice-Juice is all about now.
We are Juice-Juice!
Juice-Juice!
Hello! This time, I'm joined by Yuna Matsumoto of Angerme and Rina Ichikawa of BEYOOOOONDS Subway.
Rina Ichioka from BEYOOOOONDS Subway.
They are the two of us, so please bear with us until the end of the show.
Now, this Halo! Ste will be distributed on March 8.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will finally start next weekend on March 18.
What do you think?
Angerme will start on March 18, and BEYOOOOONDS will start on March 19.
Anjelm is releasing a new album on March 22 called "Big Love!
It has the exact same title, "Big Love!
This will be the last tour for Ms. Takeuchi, so I hope it will be a very exciting one.
We, BEYOOOOONDS, are going to perform under the title of BEYOOOOONDS Concert Tour NEO VIO, and we are looking forward to seeing what kind of new BEYOOOOONDS we can show you.
I hope you are looking forward to seeing what kind of new BEYOOOOONDS we are going to show you.
And the two groups will be performing in various places around the country on this tour.
Are there any places you are looking forward to seeing?
I'm going to Okinawa prefecture for the first time in Angeleum.
I'm going to Okinawa for the first time among the members of Angelem, so I'm really looking forward to seeing what it will be like.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what it will be like.
We, BEYOOOOONDS, are going to Yamaguchi prefecture this time.
This will be the first time for us to go there for BEYOOOOONDS's concert tour.
Also, we all love to eat, so I hope we can enjoy some delicious food.
Also, on April 1 and 2, KiNA FES and Satomi Satoyama will be holding a new event, "Think Carbon Neutral 2023", so let's have a good time together!
Let's have a good time together.
Please enjoy!
yeah
Come on
Mina Agane Mina Agane Mina
Agake Mina
Agake aupt
Come on!
Come on! Come on, get up! Get up!
Keep up! Keep going!
There's a beautiful FUTURE
Juice! Juice! We're going to Nippon Budokan!
I'll be at the Nippon Budokan!
I'm in love. I'm in despair.
No watch
Development
Boring.
I'm yawning.
Let's rewrite the scenario. Let's go.
Worldliness.
I like color.
Give me your eyes, life
You can't just be a spectator
You'll never be a spectator.
I'm the star of the show, no matter what they say
There's no way I'm going to tell anyone
Hold on tight to my heart, everyone's paying attention
I'm sure there's only one step I'll have to take to break it
Imagine the whole thing
Save bar in society
Imagine everything
Now it's just me running up
Yeah!
Yeah! ♪ Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on Keep going up!
Keep going up! Keep going up!
My future I'm looking for
I'm tempted to take it too far
But I won't show it
Synchronized spoons, on-grace to the heart
Keyword ad-lib, let me hear it
Let's go
We've got to have fun, don't we?
More than once, more than once again
Saradoshi, the dream we swore we'd achieve
You definitely want to make it come true, don't you?
No matter what tomorrow brings
Please let me shine a strong light on you.
I don't know what to do
If you still have something to reveal deep in the black, go home.
Cheers, my maid. She's beautiful.
To regrets. Wow.
Cheers, my maid. She says it's beautiful.
I've got it in my hand. To the Oak Stage.
Hypes, hype, hype.
Whatever tomorrow brings
I'm the star of the show.
Let the light shine on me
That's why I like it
Rogue of the Demon Tribe
If you're just chillin', go home
Imagine the fire
Imagine it all
Imagine the fire.
You're going to get there from the boat pen.
Let's go up, let's go up, let's go up, let's go up, let's go up
Let's go up, let's go up, let's go up
Look at the beautiful Future
Let's go up, let's go up, let's go up, let's go up
Let's go up and see what happens
See, a wonderful Future
I like you who are doing your best.I like you who are working hard.
With Yuna Matsumoto of Angerme, Yuna Matsumoto of
BEYOOOOONDS, and Rena Ichioka from Subway, Halo! sta.
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so please answer them in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
Yes, I'll do my best to keep up the tempo.
Okay, here we go.
March is a time when many people are preparing for a new life.
What would you like to start now?
Baking bread.
Your first album "Big Love" will be released on March 22!
What kind of Yuna Matsumoto can we expect to hear in this album?
Cool and cute Yuna Matsumoto!
What did you notice or learn from the experience of making your first album?
The expressive power of singing.
What is Yuna Matsumoto's best dish?
Dry curry with lots of vegetables
Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
What is your first encounter with Hello!
My mother had a live DVD of Morning Musume。 Project's live DVD that my mother had.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
I was going to ask you a question.
Um, Big Love is being released.
What kind of Yuna Matsumoto can be heard in this work?
Well, there are 8 new songs in this album.
Among them, some are cool, some are cute and some are not.
There are a lot of songs in this album, some of them are cool, some of them are cute, and some of them are not.
Please listen to them.
I hope you will listen to them and find out that I have this side of me too.
Yes, and I'm a little curious about my specialty.
Yes, it's a dry curry with lots of vegetables.
I like to make a dry curry with lots of vegetables, so that it is filled with the deliciousness of vegetables.
I started by asking, "Can you make dry curry?
I'd like to start by asking, "Can you make dry curry?
I'm not very good with vegetables.
I don't usually eat them very often.
But I think I can eat dry curry made by Wakana.
I think people who don't like vegetables can eat it too.
Yes, I think so.
Questions for Mr. Ichioka will be after the VTR.
Hello! Ste.
Halo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Ichioka a question.
Yes, I do.
I think so.
Currently in the period of using the Seishun 18 Kip
What kind of plan would you plan now?
A trip to the Hokuriku region
Today, March 8, the Blu-ray of "Theatre Girl's Club: Beauty Hiring Pay Electricity" has been released.
What do you find attractive about BEYOOOOONDS that is unique to theater?
Seeing the members of a completely different camp.
Here's my question for you.
Does it take you long to memorize your lines?
It takes me a while.
On April 12, BEYOOOOONDS will release her first new single in a year and a month!
Is there anything you think BEYOOOOONDS could have done better?
Fakes, for example.
I think everyone has improved in the singing part.
Which song from the 25 years of Hello!
Cherry Blossoms in Full Blossom
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Traveling to Hokuriku on the Seishun 18 Kip
What is it like to travel?
You can use the Seishun 18-kip for a maximum of 5 days.
If you have 5 days...
I have never been to Hokuriku area so much.
I want to go to Kanazawa first.
I'd like to go to Kanazawa first.
I want to go to Kanazawa first, and then go up a little bit.
and go back down again on the third day.
I'd like to go to Kanazawa first, and then go up a little bit and come back down again.
That would be nice.
That's what I'd like to do.
And it'll take me a while to memorize the lines I heard.
What do you think?
Well, BEYOOOOONDS isn't just for the stage.
BEYOOOOONDS has a lot of lines in her songs.
Especially in the subway song
Especially the long lines in the song "Subway"...
I'm always struggling with it.
I'm slow to learn the lines.
Many of the members are pretty fast, so it's hard for me to remember them.
I'd like to learn too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. We'll continue after this.
See you soon!
I'm Sei Fukumura from Morning Musume。 I'm Sei Fukumura of 23.
Finally, the food is ready.
I'll do my best again this week.
What are you going to cook?
Griece of pork loin.
Wow, it looks so delicious.
Smells great.
Wow! It looks perfect.
Wow! Yum!
Perfect! Cool!
Here he is.
This boy will be here soon.This girl is quick.
You don't have to sizzle.
You don't have to color
This one is normal.
This one at once with rapid fire.
I'll repeat.
That's good.
I'll be scared if it comes out at home.
It's stylish.
If it's a family birthday or something, it's stylish.
I'd like to have it as a main dish.
It has a face.
This is the front side.
This is the back side.
In the case of pork, the thin side is on the right.
This is the shape of the dish.
It's good.
Meat shrinks a lot when it's cooked.
It might warp, so we're going to cut a little slit here.
There's a lot of muscle here.
Cut it off like this. The stringy bits will shrink.
And then it's going to float, and that's where it's going to lose its color.
And if you put it at an angle...
So, this one here is the face, and this one here is the bottom.
So let me ask you this, or let me ask you the other way around.
This one, facing this way.
Burn the face first.
I see.
Now, this one here, we had one row.
But I'm going to batten this one down.
I see.
That's right, 90 degrees.
90 degrees.
The round part...
And then it pops.
The center of the round part floats.
So if you want to push it, you have to push a little bit in the middle here.
I feel like I'm not supposed to press too hard.
Do you have an image that you don't want to press too hard?
Yes, that's right.
As long as it sticks, it's fine.
That's fine.
The trick is...
Basically, the face side should be about 80%.
The back side should be about 20%.
The color will change slightly.
Especially if you're on this side.
the color will turn whitish.
When it reaches the top, it's a sign that it's done.
It's a sign that it's baked well.
It's about halfway up.
90 degrees.
Do you want me to do it?
Let's do it.
This is kind of important.
Let's see if we can do it.
This is important.
Okay, here we go.
Yes, there, there, there, yes, OK. It's floating, so just tinkle, tinkle, tinkle.
And here's what I did.
I sprinkled salt on the face, but not on the back.
The sign that it's ready to cook is that the moisture is gradually coming up to the surface, which is a signal that about 70% of the ingredients are in the pan.
It doesn't work so well. Moisture came out.
This is too thin. This is too thick.
I'm glad I didn't add oil before grilling.
The oil comes out from the pork itself.
Ready?
How was it? Good, perfect.
It looks like it's been nicely pan-fried.
This side didn't get much, did it? No.
It's a bummer.
But if you look closely, you can see that it's nicely done. It's done.
The sign of frying is when you touch it like this.
I think you could tell it was soft when I continued with the nuts.
But it's still soft.
You have to do it with your fingers.
I got a finger.
Don't worry, it's in here. It's not for food.
The flavor of the pork comes out later.
Put it on top of the potatoes.
So that the potatoes absorb the flavor of the pork.
After baking, we did this during the baking time.
But if you cut it up and say, "Okay, it's done, let's eat it now," the juices will be all dried out.
If you cut the potatoes, the juices will be all dried out.
I want the meat to go diagonally at the end.
Mushrooms, potatoes, asparagus, tomatoes, mustard
Well, that sounds difficult!
Well, let's start with the small potatoes.
You should be able to see the grill marks.
How do I do that?
Oh, yes.
Intuition.
Intuition, intuition, intuition.
And straight.
I'm gonna cut it all off.
You mean like this?
Yeah.
Just the right length.
It's wild.
A little more.A little more.
Then cut a lot!
Plenty of water
and so on.
Like this. I'm going to cut the meat.
Oh, wait, it's so tender.
It's perfect. Yay!
It's wild, isn't it? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like this in the front? Yeah, like this.
Looks so good!
Yes, it's a little bit like standing up.
Yes!
Oh, man!
And then pour this juice all over it.
Pour it over here.
Yes, sir.
It makes it shiny.
The whole thing will be shiny.
Looks so good!
Like the way it's placed?
Yes, it's all in your taste.
I think it's good.
It's great.
Over there.
It's done!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
The pork loin gruyere is done!
I had no idea! The dish turned out to be many times more beautiful and very impressive!
Wow, it's absolutely delicious!
Mmm! Mmm! Yum! Delicious!
It's delicious! Just like in a restaurant!
I even got that nice char on the top.
Delicious! It's amazing that all this is seasoned with only salt!
Lemon, celery and what was it?
Marinated iyoka!
Yum!
Delicious!
Yes, it is!
I can't believe how different it is with fruit in it!
It goes well with pork loin.
I thought he had good taste.
The way you used the knife went very well.
You didn't hesitate when you cut the meat.
Yes, I didn't hesitate.
I think that's very important.
It looks wild, but you don't hesitate.
Like with the microwave bag.
Dripping the juices from the meat.
The way of making the marinade was totally different from the way we do it at home.
I'd like to try it again at home.
Please give it a try!
Thank you very much for your time today.
It looked really delicious, didn't it?
Yes, it did.
Wakana, I know you cook on a regular basis.
How long have you been cooking? Cooking.
Yes, I have been cooking since I was in the first grade of junior high school. I started cooking when I was in the first grade of junior high school.
Is that something you already feel like helping out with?
Yes, that's right. I started cooking with the idea of helping out, and then I got into it because I wanted to serve it to my family.
It was amazing.
I was on the cooking corner of Halo! I was on the cooking corner of "Halo!
The staff said that she was really good at what she was doing.
I really respect her.
I am 9 years older than her.
I also want to do my best in cooking.
Yes, I want to cook a lot of delicious food. I want to cook a lot of delicious food.
I like to eat beautifully rather than being afraid.
Actually, I'm the right type today.
I'm just as I am. We can love each other.
Who is it? The man of my dreams?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm just pretending.
I'm freewheeling. I'm guaranteed...
I've been looking for happiness so carefully. Why?
Why? Poppin' Lovin', just curious.
Gumb tube. Unreliable.
Algorithms.
Surprise, romance.
I'm still looking for a little bit of each. I'm still looking for a little bit of each.
Poppin' Lovin', real love is a mystery
It's not about logic, after all
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Copy Rabbi
Koshi fixing your ears
Prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction, prediction
Your friends seem to think you're kind
I don't know why I'm attracted to you right now
I'm the only one who can measure it
It's more than love, it's excitement
Or else my life wouldn't be over there
I can't help it, I can't help it, I can't help it
I only want to collect your true nature
Hey!
Chabi-chabi-nato-kobushi
Love and age
Delusional ideals that can't be guessed
Even if our values are different
It's OK, it's OK
I want to be sensedI want to be sensed at least once
I went back to Chavichavi
Popetine.
You must have been miserable.
Why would I be?
It can't be.
That's not good enough.
It's not fate. It's not selfish. It's the love we've developed.
Sometimes I do it too hard, but only because I love you so much.
You're not wrong.
Hey!
Topinati, be my girl, and don't count on the gum tube.
Lucrative Rhythm
Romantic by surprise
It's a Little Sneaky
I want to be sought out
Poppin' Navi, even dyeing is nice
I want to make a mistake with your eyes
I want to be clawed and it's Sunday
Poppinavi
by H.
Poppin' Love you
Let's work hard tomorrow!
Yuka Matsumoto from Angelem and Reina Ichikawa from Beyons and Chisatachi are here with you on Halo!
Reina Ichioka of BEYOOOOONDS and Chisatachi will be presenting "Halo! stay!
Angelem will be releasing their new album "Big Love" on March 22nd!
Yes, I told you a little bit about it earlier.
What makes me me is that it includes the singles after me, distributed songs, and 8 newly recorded songs.
It is truly a big love album, so please get it and listen to it a lot!
I hope you will get it and listen to it a lot.
Yes, Beyoncé is a band.
On April 12, the 4th single, "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, Mt.
Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler Mountain
The song "In the Night Sky Where Even Dreams Cannot Be Drawn" will be released on April 12.
In the Toe of Us show that we used to do...
I have already performed "Seek Me, Fate's Traveller Mountain".
It has BEYOOOOONDS's style, but at the same time
The song "In the night sky where you can't even dream" is a little bit like a chorus song.
I think you will be able to hear the beautiful voice of the Beyons.
Please look forward to it!
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will start next weekend.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit starting next weekend, and you may be able to see our new album and new single, so please look forward to it!
Never surrender Now Never surrender
What do they know?
Never surrender Never never surrender
Never forget what you believe in
Uncharted worlds, Tigers to connect
Tears on your cheeks
What do you want to see? I'm dreaming
The eyes of your heart
Yes, I love you
You can open them more
I love you
Let's go to the lonely guest room
Unreachable Ocean Theft
As You Like It
Win Forever
Don't Stop Your Fever
Stop being free and be strong
Always Whenever
Be strong On the
On the touch of freedom
Never surrender
Never, never surrender
What the hell do they know?
Never surrender Never, Never surrender
Just remember what you believe
We've been through some hard times
But the weather's gonna change soon
Promises to carry you through, you'll get them
Today and tomorrow
HAPPY END DAYO!
Message you
I bet you were jealous.
I bet you're scared to death.
I've been useful to others
I'll fall in a row, I'll shine a light
I'll shine a light on where you're going
Shine on, challenger
Shout out YOUNG FEVER
People are fragile, so let's be strong
Even if we lose, we DON'T GIVE UP
Don't weave, don't weave, REMEMBER
Let's be strong, just for the balance
REMEMBER
If you like it
Oh Oh Oh, win Forever
Shine on, Yo! Fever
Seek freedom and be strong
Always Wherever
Stay strong, All night
Touched by inconvenience, I grow stronger
Shine on, Challenger
Run out, Yo! Fever
People are fragile, so let's be strong
Don't give up when you lose
Don't give up Remember
Don't give up
Tonight's your night, if you'd like
Don't let me sleep, don't let me sleep
♪ The first night of summer ♪ I don't want to go homeThe first night of summer, I don't want to go home.
I won't go back to sleep I won't go back to sleep
I'll never forget what I know
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you too.
Reina Ichioka of BEYOOOOONDS Subway presents Halo! Sta.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Yes, it's time to say goodbye!
On March 22nd, Angstrom's new album
Big Love will be released!
Yes, sir!
And BEYOOOOONDS will release a new single on April 12!
Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler
In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream
will be released on April 12!
And the same April 12
I was doing in the fall
BEYOOOOONDS 2nd concert tour
will be released on Blu-ray!
Yes!
Yes, and from March 18
Hello Project 2023 Spring
City Circuit will start!
Yes, and on March 18, Hello Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will start!
Anjelum Concert Tour Big Love will start on
From the 18th
BEYOOOOONDS Concert Tour Niobio
from the 19th.
And April 1st and 2nd
Well, you see, at Makuhari Messe
Hina Fest and Satoyama Satoumi advocate
A new event
Think Carbon Neutral
2023 will be held
What we can do
In the Satoyama-Satoumi Movement
Carbon Neutrality and Our Lives!
Please come to the venue!
Hallo! Ste.
Hello Project members
Project members will appear on the channel more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
We are still in the midst of a difficult time.
Let's get through it together!
This time, I'll be talking with
Shigeru Matsumoto of Angelem and
and Rina Ichioka of Lyons Subway.
Farewell.